yo wes ono the day awesome reply you say
never change feel that you needed me
[Music]
just over time Paintings on the
Hai aku yang nih calm scene with us
out jauh Reunion Dino the sheikh's see
you win it huh huh hey syai-aa
Hai Putri Duyung jauh Sheikh lemu-lemu
[Applause]
see you you aquifer Okay detail
snow needs such H2O
ke4 Ade Rocky I really uvuvwevwevwe
[Music]
uvuvwevwevwe tested By Me
nyenyuh hyungmu smile smile smile
today still much more smile you
sad Really you Daud bereueh
[Music]
Indonesia according
Hi closed have Facebook this type
really you Daud bereueh finished
losing your smile
[Applause]
[Music] hi hi